vancitybuzz.com 2012-05-12

# Privacy Policy | Vancity Buzz | Vancouver Blog

We will not sell, distribute, barter, or transfer any of your personally identifiable information to companies, organizations or other parties outside of Buzz Connected Media Inc. (“BCM”) and its subsidiaries (i.e. VancityBuzz.com) without your permission.

This statement covers BCM. Please read this statement carefully. Your use of BCM indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

**Information Collection**

BCM is the sole owner of the information collected. BCM may collect information from our users at several different points on our web site.

**Comments**

In order to enhance their use of this web site, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must submit information including a valid email address. BCM will not pass this information to any other organization. Please see [Comment Policy](http://www.vancitybuzz.com/comment-policy/).

**Cookies**

We may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Some of our advertisers may also use cookies on our site. However, BCM has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this web site are delivered by different services including but not limited to Google. Information about users’ visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not name, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. Please see information on [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

**Log Files**

Like most standard web sites, we maintain log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, BCM may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.

**Business Transitions**

In the event BCM goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**

The BCM web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, BCM, are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by BCM.

**Notification of Changes**

Whenever BCM changes our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@vancitybuzz.com.
